GODSPOWER IFFITIS

E: godspoweriffitis@gmail.com

P: 07080583634

A: Oshodi/Isolo, Lagos

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hardworking individual experienced in Project management. Gifted in event coordination, scheduling and correspondence. Maintains professional appearance and demeanor and expertly completes assigned tasks with focus on quality. Dependable and quick-learning team player with effective communication and organization skills.

WORK HISTORY

Glistars Concept - Project Manager

Lagos, Nigeria • 06/2021 - 12/2021

- Met project deadlines without sacrificing build quality or workplace safety.
- Updated operational methods and oversaw accounting procedures for improved efficiency.
- Maintained relationships with developers to lower costs and diversify capabilities.
- Provided detailed technical and operational direction in project challenges, consistently meeting deliverables according to deadlines.

Codevixen Academy - Content Creation Instructor Lagos, Nigeria • 07/2021 - 10/2021

- Collaborated with students to complete homework assignments, identify lagging skills and correct weaknesses.
- Planned lessons for allotted time to strengthen weak subjects and build skills.
- Developed student confidence through positive reinforcement strategies.
- Leveraged technology to accelerate learning by proving students with easy-to-access information.

SKILLS

- Communication
- Meeting planning
- Executive presentations
- Multitasking
- Project Management
- Attention to details
- Problem-solving
- Content Creation
- Analytical and Critical Thinking
- Negotiation Skills

EDUCATION

University of Cape Coast

Ghana • 05/2017

Bachelor of Science: Management And Computer Studies

CERTIFICATIONS

- Project Portfolio Management Foundations – PMI (Authorized trainer)
- Leading and Working in Teams LinkedIn
- Content Creation Instructor Codevixen
- Entrepreneurship Training and Coaching – SEDIN
- Certificate of National Service NYSC
- Software Development Training YIN

L'Hotel D'Ami - Executive Assistant

Yenagoa, Bayelsa • 09/2020 - 05/2021

- Used advanced software to prepare documents, reports and presentations.
- Organized and coordinated conferences and monthly meetings.
- Created expense reports, budgets and filing systems for management team.
- Facilitated training and onboarding for incoming office staff.

Empower Bayelsa - Assistant Team Lead

Yenagoa, Bayelsa • 08/2018 - 09/2019

- Developed process improvements and offered actionable solutions to correct recurring issues.
- Coordinated weekly meetings for internal and external groups.
- Mentored and guided candidates to maintain focus and ensure completion of program.
- Built strong relationships with partners and stakeholders through positive attitude and attentive response.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Collaborated with a team of 10 to organize the Empower Bayelsa project, the most significant free skill acquisition program in Nigeria by a group of individuals with over 800 participants.
- Successfully assisted top level management to increase revenue by 40% in a month.
- Won the "Beyond The Now" business grant.
- Collaborated with a team of seven to develop a proposed online voting system for Bayelsa State Government in two weeks.
- Awarded the Most Influential Youth in NYSC Akwa Ibom.

REFERENCE

Available on request.